How often do you check your phone?
你多久查看一次手机呢？
According to a study led by Nottingham Trent University in Britain, the average person looks at their device 85 times a day, browsing the internet or using apps.
根据英国诺丁汉特伦特大学主导的一项研究，普通人每天会查看自己的手机85次，浏览互联网或者使用应用程序。
Updating their status on social media platforms also made people reach for their electronic companion frequently.
在社交媒体平台上更新自己的状态也使得人们频繁地拿起他们的电子伙伴（手机）。
Even the study's participants thought that was a lot: this figure is twice as often as they thought they did.
甚至这项研究的参与者都认为这个次数很多：这个数字是他们认为的两倍。
Our phones might be shaping our behaviour more than we realise, and changing the way we interact with people right next to us.
我们的手机对我们行为的塑造可能比我们意识到的要多，并且正在改变我们与身边人互动的方式。
Do you actually look at your surroundings more than at your phone?
你实际上是更多地关注周围环境还是手机呢？
Is it rude to check your phone when someone is talking to you?
当有人跟你说话时查看手机是不是不礼貌呢？
Sherry Turkle interviewed hundreds of college students about this.
雪莉·特克尔就此采访了数百名大学生。
She's a clinical psychologist and a professor of social studies at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology.
她是一名临床心理学家，也是麻省理工学院的社会学教授。
They talked about something they called 'the rule of three'.
他们谈到了一个他们称之为“三规则”的东西。
The rule has to do with being considerate to others in spite of the allure of the little flat box.
这个规则与在那个小小的扁平盒子（手机）的诱惑下仍然对他人体贴有关。
Turkle explains: "If you go to dinner with friends, you don't want to look down at your phone until you see that three people are looking up in the conversation.
特克尔解释说：“如果你和朋友去吃晚餐，你不应该低头看手机，直到看到有三个人在抬头交谈。
So there's a new etiquette where you don't look down unless three people are looking up in order to keep a little conversation alive."
所以有了一个新的礼仪，即你不要低头，除非有三个人抬头，这样才能让交谈继续下去。”
Actually, if you are clever enough you might use your phone as a tool to connect with people next to you.
实际上，如果你足够聪明，你可以把手机当作与身边人建立联系的工具。
How about showing them pictures stored in its memory?
给他们看看手机里存储的照片怎么样呢？
Sharing a bit of your life with them can bring you closer together.
和他们分享一点你的生活可以让你们的关系更亲密。
And you can also invite everyone to take a selfie with you.
你还可以邀请每个人和你一起拍自拍。
But the best thing to deal with mobile phone addiction is to go cold turkey and leave the machine behind occasionally or just switch it off and keep it firmly in your pocket for a while.
但是应对手机成瘾的最好办法是突然戒掉，偶尔把手机放在一边，或者干脆关掉手机，把它牢牢地放在口袋里一段时间。
Who knows... 'life' might be what happens when you are too busy staring at a small screen.
谁知道呢……当你忙于盯着小屏幕时，“生活”可能就在悄然流逝。